mysitemapgenerator.com 2019-10-18

# Privacy Policy - My Sitemap Generator

General provisions

This Privacy policy establishes the procedure for the receipt, storage, processing, use and disclosure of user personal data.

**By using or accessing our services in any way, you acknowledge that you accept the procedures described in the Privacy policy and provide your consent to the collection and processing of your personal data.**

Collection and use of personal data

We collect and store personal data (such as your name and email address) that you knowingly transmit to us. We collect certain types of personal data (such as IP address and information about your browser) automatically when you use our website.

When using the services of this website, the following personal data is processed: the data provided by the user both when filling in electronic forms and in the process of using services.

Only those personal data (such as first and last name, access passwords, email addresses, telephone numbers, etc.) that are knowingly and voluntarily provided by users for the purposes of using the services are subject to collection and use.

Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are sent from a website and stored on a user's device. Please note that full-fledged work with our website is only available when using cookies. Disabling cookies may result in restricted access to content or to services not functioning properly.

Our website uses the following types of cookies:

**Mandatory cookies** are required to provide certain website features and services, such as access to secure pages, registration, and authorization.

**Operational cookies** allow us to obtain information about how users use our website, such as how often a particular feature or service is used.

**Functional cookies** are used to store the settings and configurations you have set for our website for a long time, such as the choice of interface language.

Some partner services, such as payment systems, social networks, and web-analytics services, are integrated with our website. Our partners may install their own cookies on user device while visiting our website.

Please note that our Privacy policy does not cover the use of third-party cookies and we are not responsible for their privacy policies and operation.

You can configure your device to prevent or restrict the receipt of cookies by using the features available in your browser.

Protection of personal data

We use generally accepted standards of technological and operational protection of information and personal data against loss, misuse, distortion or destruction. 

We do not transfer personal data to third parties unless such transfer is a requirement of the law.

Period of retaining personal data

We retain your personal data for the entire lifetime of the user account on our website. Further, we reserve the right to store some information about you in an impersonal or generalized form that excludes the possibility of identifying your identity.

Personal data of minors

Please note that we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information about persons who have not reached the age of 14, or who are under 16 years old in countries subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). If you are under the age of 14 or, if applicable, 16 years, please do not register on our website or send us your personal data.

Your rights in relation to your personal data

You have the right to update, access, modify or delete personal data, revoke consent to the processing of personal data that you have provided under this Privacy policy.

In the event of any comments, requests or claims regarding personal data that we have processed, you may contact us through the means of communication available on the website or through the contact information published on the website. In some cases, we may need additional information from you that may include personal data if it is required to verify your identity.

x

This website uses cookies. Using this website means you're agreeing with this. More info Accept
